gogo-power.com 2014-05-20

# gogo power Privacy Policy for customer

**Privacy Policy**

**Information Collection and Use**

Gogo-power.com is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. If you elect to receive our newsletter or special promotions, your contact information will be used for the delivery of these items. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**

When you make a purchase from our site you can choose to open an account, which will allow you to store your billing and shipping information on our servers or you can check out without opening an account. If you choose to set up an account you will provide your name, email address, credit card information, address, and phone number and will select a password. After you set up your account, the next time you enter our Site you can log in by entering your email address and password and your billing and shipping information is automatically completed. We do not store your credit card number for your security. Whether you open an account or not, on checkout you can sign up to receive our newsletter to keep you informed about our latest offers, current promotions, specials and new additions to the Gogo-power.com site. See Choice/Opt-out below to learn how you may change your preferences. If you send us an email through the "Contact Us" page, we use your email address to respond to your question. We do not save the address of emails we receive after we have responded. If you choose to shop without opening an account your information will be retained only as long as needed to process and fulfill your order, in most cases it is deleted after three months.

**How we use your personal information.**

We use the information you provide when shopping on our Site to process your orders, to keep you updated on your orders and to personalize your shopping experience. In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by reputable third-party banking and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card and to process your order. They are under contractual obligation to keep your personal information private and are not permitted to use or share your information for their own purposes including marketing. We use your email address to send you our newsletters if you ask to be placed on our list. We may share aggregated statistics not linked to any individual about buying patterns, sales and other shopping information with our marketing partners.

**Security**

Our secure servers protect sensitive data including your credit card information using SSL encryption and firewall technology to protect your personal information from being read as it travels to our ordering system. Information sent to us by email is not encrypted and is therefore not secure. While we take reasonable measures to prevent the loss or misuse of the information that you provide to us, including but not limited to, your Personally Identifiable Information, due to factors beyond our control, we do not guarantee that your Personally Identifiable Information or any other information collected by us will be completely secure from misappropriation by hackers or other third parties or from other criminal activities. If you have any questions or concerns about Gogo-power.com's security practices, you can send us an email at [gogopower.com@gmail.com](mailto:gogopower.com@gmail.com)

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. 

Like most websites, we use "cookies" to keep track of your current shopping session, to personalize your experience and so that you may retrieve your shopping cart at any time. However, we do NOT use cookies to examine your surfing behavior before or after you leave our Site. There are products commercially available that are designed to help you disable cookies. Although we want you to be aware that such products exist, please note that if you choose to use them we will not be able to provide you with a personalized service, and it may result in certain features and services not being available to you. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. It is used solely for purposes of processing your order and is not shared with any third parties.

**Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties. 

**Sharing**

We use other third parties to provide shipping and credit card processing services on our site. When you purchase a product(s) on our site, we will share your contact, shipping and credit card information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing purposes.

_UPS Corporate Headquarters_  
55 Glenlake Parkway, NE  
Atlanta , GA 30328  
United States  
[www.ups.com](http://www.ups.com/) | _US_ _Postal Service Headquarters_  
475 L'Enfant Plaza, SW  
Washington DC  
1-800-ASK-USPS  
---|---  
  
**Child Privacy**

Because of the nature of our business, our products and services are not designed to appeal to children, and therefore we do not knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from children. Our terms and conditions of use require that any registration may only be made by those over the age of 16. By using our services, you are representing that you are at least 16 years of age or have the permission from a parent or legal guardian to use our service. If we know that information is being provided by a child under the age of 16, then we will not collect the information without parental consent or parent notification, which will include the opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information or to prevent the child's participation in the activity. Without parental consent, online information will only be used to respond to an unsolicited request and for no other purposes. We recognize that protecting children's identities and privacy online is important and that the responsibility to do so rests with both the online industry and with parents. 

We encourage parents or guardians to monitor the use of this Site by children to insure that they are not exposed to material that the parent or guardian may find objectionable. Parents are also encouraged to use parental control capabilities within their internet software to assist in their efforts to limit access to certain sites.

**Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Gogo-power.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

If you have opted out of receiving communications from Gogo-power.com, you will still be able to view news of policy changes at [www.Gogo-power.com](http://www.newegg.com/). Otherwise, you may e-mail us at [gogopower.com@gmail.com](mailto:gogopower.com@gmail.com) to ask our customer service department about changes and updates. 

**Last Update**

The Privacy Policy contained herein became officially effective September 1, 2008 

**Contacting Us** : If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, would like more information, or if you believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](mailto:gogopower.com@gmail.com) or write to: 

imagestore us inc

7706 18th ave, Brooklyn, NY 11214
